

XRAVE110

## **CONTACTS**



+48-577-082-718



xRave110@protonmail.com



portfolio-xrave110.vercel.app



A Jablonka, Poland

## **Technologies**

C, Python, Solidity

Javascript

### Toolsets/Frameworks

Pytest

Brownie, Hardhat/Ethers

Web3, OpenZeppelin, Git

Truffle, React

#### Other skills

Polish

DeFi. Chainlink utils

English, Ethereum, ISTQB

**NFTs** 

#### Education

2012-2017

**Cracov University of Technology** Cracov

Electrical engineering with major in Electric Control Devices in full-time mode of study.

# KAMIL PALENIK

**SOFTWARE ENGINEER** 

#### **PROFILE**

I am a Software Engineer with 5 years experience in automotive industry. In 2019 I got interested in blockchain technology, especially in DeFi and I have been using DeFi protocols ever since. I was absolutely amazed how it works without any intermediares just maths and peers.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Dec 2019 - Now

#### Blockchain learning/development

Smart contracts development with brownie and unit/integration tests. One year course with Moralis Academy concerning smart contracts development, web3 interaction and web development. New projects development which consolidated skills and extended them to multiple frameworks and toolsets.

Apr 2022 - Aug 2022

#### **Embedded System Software Integrator**

Nexteer Automotive

Integration tests development. Components integration and configuration Autosar stack.

Nov 2019 - Mar 2022

#### **Embedded System Software Engineer**

**Nexteer Automotive** 

Developing and testing software components using C, Python and Reactis/Matlab. Incorporating unit and integration testing for CAN messages.

Jun 2019 - Oct 2019

## **Embedded Software Engineer**

VECTOR MICROSAR changes in basic software components (DEM, DCM). The same responsibilities as the previous role.

Oct 2017 - May 2019

## **Junior Embedded Software Engineer**

Application component software development. Performing static and dynamic unit tests for components. Modeling software using SysML/UML.